

# Evgenii Denisov

Phone: +382-67-559608

E-mail: evgenij.denisov@gmail.com

Telegram: <u>@el71Gato</u> — preferred means of communication LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/evgenii-denisov-748b10129

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/elGato">https://github.com/elGato</a> Location: Montenegro, ready to relocate.

## **Desired position: Gameplay Developer**

**Employment**: staffer or entrepreneur contract.

**Skills**: Gameplay prototyping and implementation, Web API.

Technologies: Python, Go, JS, C++, UE, Git, Perforce.

**Summary**: A strong game developer who also has a lot of experience in web backend. Implementing best practices intuitively because they just feel natural. Sometimes developing games solo just for fun. Even playing games or using software, always thinking how to implement them.

## Work experience (> 8 years total)

**LimeCity** (webgl.limecity.online): June 2024 – now

#### **Gameplay Backend Developer** (Python, DRF)

Developing a mobile city builder game in a small team. Implemented mechanics:

- Garden: planting, watering, harvesting.
- Pet dog: feed it to boost production efficiency, and it can find some valuables.
- Daily quests: do simple tasks to get XP on another website.
- Daily login rewards: get a streak for bigger rewards.

**V4Scale** (v4scale.com): November 2023 – September 2024 (10 months)

#### Python / Golang Backend Developer (FastAPI, gRPC)

Maintained an information security management system with an international team. Cannot reveal more.

**Zubr** (Saint Petersburg, zubr.io): July 2020 – February 2023 (2 years 7 months)

#### Python Backend Developer (FastAPI, gRPC, Kafka)

Maintained a cryptocurrency derivative exchange with a team. It was a complex ecosystem of services with asynchronous data flow. Maintained a dozen services and made several new ones. When the exchange experienced a critical data error that could have cost the company several BTC, modified several services to maintain data consistency even after such errors.

HCF Bank (Saint Petersburg, market.homecredit.ru): September 2018 – April 2020 (1 year 8 months)

### Python Backend Developer / ML Specialist (Django, Celery, PostgreSQL, Keras)

Maintained an installment goods marketplace with a team. Split a monolith codebase into services and microservices. Removed a neural network from the feed parsing to speed up the process from several minutes to several seconds per feed. Reworked a 200 lines SQL query that nobody remembered how it works to speed it up from 20 to 7 minutes and made it readable.

**Avatarico** (Saint Petersburg, avatarico.com): January 2018 – June 2018 (6 months)

#### Python Backend Developer / ML Specialist (DRF, NLTK, PyTorch)

Being a sole Python developer and ML specialist in the company, self-studied both professions and developed an entertaining artificial neural network imitating a chat user.

**220 Volt** (Saint Petersburg, www.220-volt.ru): December 2015 – October 2017 (1 year 10 months)

#### **QA Engineer** (Postman, Yandex.Tank, pytest)

Was a proactive member of the team. Both checked new functionality and made proposals about adding, removing amd modifying the product features. Wrote autotests and dabbled into new technologies. Adopted and introduced Gitlab CI and Docker before they went mainstream.

#### Education

Higher (2013): South Federal University, Information Security Faculty, Telecom Information Security.